That our saints and facts will tell
you what happened, friend, will you win something, my friend, if you
tell me some setting, then whom will you tell this
tonight, you know that my parents'
health is not good, so I am very
worried that if any emergency
situation arises, then how will I take care of their expenses
because you also know that the condition of my house is
very bad, I can
understand, but Jigar, you got your first surgery done
last year, I have never done this health
insurance, I have
seen it for 30 years, it is very necessary, I
told you in time also
how many charts the hospitals make nowadays and Kumar also
when my husband calmed me down, from that day till
today I had to pay some
hospital bill, so because of this you are quickly
purchasing insurance, I had
heard about others and I have been reading
many places and have
only seen its advertisements, but now I get very
confused as to what is the benefit
and what is the center, I get confused, you
can understand, when I had a lot of alarm in
his village, my  I have been in
contact with him for years and was
advised to go to Ghumani and today's time was present in, I
can do the work for you, I will
give you my debit card number, so
contact them, today people
type cash for purchases, festivals etc.
and today we will make an insurance plan, now the
tension is gone, let's go and have tea, whatever has happened, do it.